本字幕由✿花語&千夏字幕組✿共同製作
Why did I trust him?
なんで信じたんだ
With my own hands, I'll...
あいつを この手で...
It's me.
俺だ
Still not interested, huh?
また興味なしってか?
Hey, why are we letting him live?
な なんで生かしとくんだ
He killed the don.
ドンをやりやったんだろう
How should I know?
知るか
Florida, a paradise...
憧れのフロリダ...
Ridiculous.
くだらね
That's the end of the Vanettis, I guess.
ヴァネッティも もう終わりだな
It's perfect for the presentation of Don Strega.
ドン ストレーガのお披露目にはお誂え向き
Hey, cut it out.
おい やめとけ
What's the big deal? He's not gonna eat it.
いいだろう どうせ食わねんだから
Let's get started!
じゃ早速
kanjou ni tsukeru
I can assign whatever name I wish
namae wa jiyuu dane
To these emotions.
hora kawarihateta
See, they've already ceased to change.
kesenai boku no
The trigger of
tsumi no hikigane ga
My unrepentable sins
toketeshimaisou de
Seems ready to melt away,
nikushimi ga kieteshimattara
But if this hatefulness fades,
kimi o korosenai kara
I'll lose my chance to kill you.
kako o tannou shiteiru
I'm experiencing every moment of my past,
tsumi ga tsukutta boku ni kawaru tame ni
Trying to become the person who created these sins
ASL no naifu de
With an ASL knife.
kioku no signal kizamareteru noni
Despite the signal carved into my memories,
itami sae keshisatteshimau kizuna no spiral
Even the pain is erased away by this spiral of causality.
Having wandered in, I begin to fade... ceasing to be myself.
mayoikonda boku wa boku de kietekureteiku
Slipping Through the Dirty Sky
穿過骯髒的天空
Throw down your weapons and come out.
武器を捨てて出てこい
If you do as we say, we won't hurt you.
おとなしく従えば 悪いようにはしない
Please, don't shoot!
頼む 打たないでくれ
We're coming out now!
今から出て行く
Those Galassia guys keep coming in swarms.
ガラッシアの野郎ともわんさか来やがって
Even if all our bullets hit, we wouldn't have enough.
全部当たっても タマが足りね
It's about time.
そろそろ頃合だ
Sticking it out any longer won't—
これ以上粘っても...
It's me.
俺だ
Hotel Lawless. Room 501.
ホテル ローレス 501号室だ
Everyone's been sent over to the Island.
皆アイランドにであらってるぜ
Are you going?
行くのか?
Yeah, you guys should get out of here as well.
お前らもここを出ろ
Who wants to die in the same place Fango did?
ファンゴの死に場所でくたばるなんて ぞっとしね
Good point.
そうだな
You're the one they're after, anyway.
そもそも あいつらのお目当てはお前だしね
Later.
じゃあな
Hey, Nero.
な ネロ
This will be our...
これが俺たちの...
Never mind.
まぁ いいや...
When you see him, sock him one for me too, okay?
やつに会ったら 俺の分も殴っておいてくれ
So, where are we going?
さて どこ行くよ
There's no way we can get away from the Galassias anyway.
どうせ ガラッシアから逃げ切れねけどな
Why are you here?
なんでお前がここにいる
What about you? Why are you still alive?
そういうお前は なんで生きてんだよ
You wanted revenge against the Vanettis, right?
ヴァネッティの奴等に復讐したがったんだよう
And you finished that crap already, right?
そんなもん もうとっくに終わってんじゃねか?
Hey, you listening to me?
おい 聞いてんのかよ?
He never wanted to join the family.
あいつはな ファミリーなんかに入りたくなかった
わざわざ儲け話持ってってやっても
Even when I told him how rich he could get,
he wouldn't even think about it.
見向きもしね
It was stupid how damn straight-laced he was.
バカみたいに真面目な奴だった
But you... You drove him crazy.
なのに お前のせいでおかしくなっちまった
You killed him.
お前に殺されちまった
He'd never even been with a woman...
女も知らねのに...
あいつが死んでお前が生きてんのは
How is it right that you live and he dies?!
なんか可笑しくねか?
Hey, are you listening?!
聞いてんのかよ おい
Pipe down.
うるすうぞ
Who's the one who sent it?
差出人は誰だ
Ganzo.
ガンゾ
So I was being deceived from all sides, huh?
寄ってたかって騙されてたって訳か
テスタラグーザの息子がこの手紙を受け取って
The son of Testa Lagusa received
this letter and returned to Lawless.
ローレスに戻ってきた
And then...
そして...
Frate...
フラテも
Volpe...
ボルペも
Del Toro...
デルトルも
Barbero...
バルベルも
Vanno...
フンノも
I killed them all.
皆俺が殺した
I'm the only person named in this letter who's still alive.
この手紙の中で 生き残ってるのは俺一人だ
Why didn't you kill me?
なぜやらなかった
Vincent holed up in his mansion and wouldn't come out.
ヴィンセントは屋敷に籠って出てこない
Obviously, I had to get close to his son first.
まずその息子に近づくのは当然だろう
That day, at the playhouse...
あの日 劇場で
You shouldn't have needed me alive anymore.
もう俺を生かしておく必要はなかったはずだ
I wanted you and Vincent to feel the same pain I did.
お前とヴィンセントには俺と同じ苦しみを
A pain worse than death.
死ぬ以上の苦しみを与えるつもりだった
A shame Vincent died so soon though.
残念ながら ヴィンセントはくたばったけどな
I-Idiot! Don't start that here!
ばばばがやろう こんなとこでおっぱじめんじゃねい
Do it.
やれよ
I'll save it for later.
お預けだ
Acting like he understands everything...
悟ったような面しやがって
Sheesh... You mafia guys...
ったく マフィアってやつは
That's the stuff.
きくな
Here, a pick-me-up.
ほれ 景気付けに
You know the saying? "Choke on your wine, you'll make it out fine."
知ってるか 酒で噎せると生き残るってと
No need to worry.
心配ずね
Mr. Tigre...
テグルさん
The boat's all ready.
艇の準備ができました
Great. Now it's goodbye, Lawless!
これでローレスはおさらばで
Go on ahead!
先に行け
Hey!
Go! Run for the boat!
行け 船まで走るだ
Hey, I'm right here! Bring it on!
ほらほら こっちだ かかってこいだ
Hey, take another look around!
おい もう一回見てこい
The king's arms are long, Nero.
王の手は長いぞ ネロ
Want to get some breakfast?
そろそろ朝飯でも食うぐあ
Awfully trusting, isn't he?
お人好しの野郎だぜ
Hey, are you kidding me?
おい まじか
Whoa, wait... Hey!
は ちょ は...
You two! Hey!
お前ら おい...
Wait! Wh-What? What? What?! Hey!
ちょ なななに おい ちょ
A-Are you kidding me?!
ま まじか
I'm hungry.
腹減った
Why did you shoot Don Galassia?
なぜ ドンガラシアを撃った
He had a good, full life, right?
もう十分人生を楽しんだろう
He was in high spirits to the very end.
最後まで上機嫌だった
What?
なんだと
It was convenient.
都合が良かった
The Vanettis killed my family.
俺はバネッチィの奴らに家族を殺された
And now we're crushing the Vanettis.
そのバネッチィは俺たちに潰される
You really manipulated all of us, didn't you?
まんまとお前に利用されたってわけだ?
Why did you save me?
何故助けた
I wanted to thank you.
礼が言いたくてなぁ
I'm the next don.
次のドンは俺だ
You really sped up my plans.
お前のおかげで随分予定が早まった
Hey, watch it!
危ねぇじゃねぇか
Shut up and start shooting!
うるせ  黙って撃ってろ
Damn it!
くそやろ
The Vanettis fled to the Island.
バネッチィの奴らはアイランドに逃げ込んだ
お前が寝てる間に
While you were asleep.
Prohibition will end soon.
もうすぐ禁酒法も終わる
That town won't be worth anything anymore.
あんな町にはなんの価値もなくなる
Why bother?
なんでわざわざ...
Nero killed Ronaldo.
ネロはロナルドの敵だ
But I think you might be more useful,
だが使いみちはお前のほうが有りそうだ
being a man with no inconvenient ambitions.
余計な野心もない
If you kill a certain someone over there, you can be free.
あそこにる誰かさんをやれば お前は自由になれる
Will you come with me?
一緒に来るか
I don't care anymore.
もう どうでもいいことだ
Looks delicious!
うまそうだ
I'm escorting a dangerous prisoner.
凶悪犯を護送中だ
Best not to stare at him too much.
あんまジロジロ見ない方がいい
Everyone who's gotten involved with him has ended up dead.
此奴に関わった奴は みんな死んじまった
Good meal.
ご馳走さん
Go right.
右だ
Go south, and you'll end up on Route 41.
南に向かえば41号に出る
And where are we going?
どこに行くつもりだ
The ocean.
海
Have you ever seen it?
見たことあるか
Nah.
いや
Why didn't you just leave the city?
なんで さっさと町を出なかった
I wanted to see my revenge play out.
復讐を見届ける為だ
Were you satisfied?
満足したか
I thought that by completing my revenge and making my family's killers pay,
復讐を果たし 家族の死に報いれば
I would find a reason to live again.
生きる理由を取り戻せると思った
But there was nothing left.
だが何も残らなかった
It was all for nothing.
すべては無駄事
You've got to be kidding me.
ふざけんなぁ
Don't you dare try to sum it all up like that.
そんな言葉で片付けじゃねぁ
What about them?! What were their deaths for?!
彼奴等は 彼奴等の死は一体なんだったんだよ
Why didn't you kill me?
なんで俺殺さなかった
I trusted you!
お前を信じてたんだぞ
Then you should have just killed me back then!
だったら俺をあの時殺してれば良かっただろう
That night, seven years ago...
七年前のあの夜
If you'd just shot me...
お前が俺を撃っつれば
You don't need a reason to live.
生きてる事に理由なんていらねぇ
You just live.
ただ生きるだけだ
The reason I didn't kill you
俺がお前を殺さなかったのは
is because I didn't want to kill you.
お前を殺したくなかったからだ